[{"answer": " When is that game going to be over?  Ive already cleaned up the house, now I", "docId": "08-07", "aSentId": 16, "question": "", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " Huh?  What do you mean?  Waiting on me for what", "docId": "08-07", "aSentId": 20, "question": " When is that game going to be over?  Ive already cleaned up the house, now I", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " What!  You said you would take me to the mall this Saturday.  I finished all th", "docId": "08-07", "aSentId": 21, "question": " Huh?  What do you mean?  Waiting on me for what", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " Huh?  Oh, he should have caught that", "docId": "08-07", "aSentId": 25, "question": " What!  You said you would take me to the mall this Saturday.  I finished all th", "qSentId": 24},{"answer": " Are you even listening to me?  What did I just say", "docId": "08-07", "aSentId": 26, "question": " Huh?  Oh, he should have caught that", "qSentId": 25},{"answer": " You said, Are you even listening to me", "docId": "08-07", "aSentId": 27, "question": " Are you even listening to me?  What did I just say", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " Karl", "docId": "08-07", "aSentId": 28, "question": " You said, Are you even listening to me", "qSentId": 27},{"answer": " Couldnt you wait just a second?  The game is almost over.  Theres only a fe", "docId": "08-07", "aSentId": 32, "question": " Karl", "qSentId": 31},{"answer": " Fine", "docId": "08-07", "aSentId": 37, "question": " Couldnt you wait just a second?  The game is almost over.  Theres only a fe", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": "This game is really important.  If we lose this game, we wont be able to play fo", "docId": "08-07", "aSentId": 38, "question": " Fine", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " What do you mean, we?  You wont play any", "docId": "08-07", "aSentId": 42, "question": "This game is really important.  If we lose this game, we wont be able to play fo", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " Dont be silly, June.  You know when I say that I just mean the team Im rootin", "docId": "08-07", "aSentId": 43, "question": " What do you mean, we?  You wont play any", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " Oh, is this a playoff game?  Is that why youre watching this and not spendin", "docId": "08-07", "aSentId": 48, "question": " Dont be silly, June.  You know when I say that I just mean the team Im rootin", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " Actually, there arent any playoffs in college football, so the whole season is lik", "docId": "08-07", "aSentId": 52, "question": " Oh, is this a playoff game?  Is that why youre watching this and not spendin", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " Ok, so how much time is left now?  We can go out when the game i", "docId": "08-07", "aSentId": 56, "question": " Actually, there arent any playoffs in college football, so the whole season is lik", "qSentId": 55},{"answer": " NO!  The other team tied the game up and the clock ran out", "docId": "08-07", "aSentId": 57, "question": " Ok, so how much time is left now?  We can go out when the game i", "qSentId": 56},{"answer": "Good, the clock says zero so the game is over now.  Lets go", "docId": "08-07", "aSentId": 58, "question": " NO!  The other team tied the game up and the clock ran out", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " Whoa, hold on.  You cant end a football game with a tie.  They have to pla", "docId": "08-07", "aSentId": 59, "question": "Good, the clock says zero so the game is over now.  Lets go", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " Overtime!  How long is that going to take?  Im starting to get angry", "docId": "08-07", "aSentId": 63, "question": " Whoa, hold on.  You cant end a football game with a tie.  They have to pla", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " Look, Im sorry.  I cant control it.  I really dont know how long it will take", "docId": "08-07", "aSentId": 64, "question": " Overtime!  How long is that going to take?  Im starting to get angry", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " Hey!  Im not gonna wait that long!  You said we could go to the mall togethe", "docId": "08-07", "aSentId": 68, "question": " Look, Im sorry.  I cant control it.  I really dont know how long it will take", "qSentId": 67},{"answer": " It wasnt the same game all day.  I was watching a different game earlier.  But", "docId": "08-07", "aSentId": 72, "question": " Hey!  Im not gonna wait that long!  You said we could go to the mall togethe", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " Im getting sick of this.  Youd better make this up to me", "docId": "08-07", "aSentId": 76, "question": " It wasnt the same game all day.  I was watching a different game earlier.  But", "qSentId": 75},{"answer": " Please dont be mad.  Look, we just scored another touchdown and got the extr", "docId": "08-07", "aSentId": 77, "question": " Im getting sick of this.  Youd better make this up to me", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " So is the game over yet", "docId": "08-07", "aSentId": 83, "question": " Please dont be mad.  Look, we just scored another touchdown and got the extr", "qSentId": 82},{"answer": " Well, now the other team gets a chance to score.  Really, it shouldnt be muc", "docId": "08-07", "aSentId": 84, "question": " So is the game over yet", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": " Ill give you five minutes. Then, I will leave without you and be very angry for th", "docId": "08-07", "aSentId": 90, "question": " Well, now the other team gets a chance to score.  Really, it shouldnt be muc", "qSentId": 89},{"answer": " OK, OK.  Five minutes, then well leave.  Oh!  They scored a touchdown too!  No", "docId": "08-07", "aSentId": 92, "question": " Ill give you five minutes. Then, I will leave without you and be very angry for th", "qSentId": 91},{"answer": " Tied again!  This could go on forever.  Lets go", "docId": "08-07", "aSentId": 96, "question": " OK, OK.  Five minutes, then well leave.  Oh!  They scored a touchdown too!  No", "qSentId": 95},{"answer": " Alright, alright.  Hey, do you mind if I listen to the game on the radio in the car", "docId": "08-07", "aSentId": 97, "question": " Tied again!  This could go on forever.  Lets go", "qSentId": 96},{"answer": " What!  Fine.  Im really getting sick of football season.  When is it over", "docId": "08-07", "aSentId": 98, "question": " Alright, alright.  Hey, do you mind if I listen to the game on the radio in the car", "qSentId": 97},{"answer": " The last regular college game is in November, but then there are special games i", "docId": "08-07", "aSentId": 99, "question": " What!  Fine.  Im really getting sick of football season.  When is it over", "qSentId": 98},{"answer": " Oh no.  How many more weekends must we do this", "docId": "08-07", "aSentId": 104, "question": " The last regular college game is in November, but then there are special games i", "qSentId": 103}]
